<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- name="generator" content="pyblosxom/1.5.3" -->
<!DOCTYPE rss PUBLIC "-//Netscape Communications//DTD RSS 0.91//EN" "http://my.netscape.com/publish/formats/rss-0.91.dtd">

<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
<title>l4x.org   </title>
<link>https://l4x.org</link>
<description>Home of Jan Dittmer</description>
<language>en</language>
<item>
  <title>MP3_Compare</title>
  <link>https://l4x.org/projects/MP3_Compare.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[

Today I found some old forgotten pages about MP3 Compare and as a nice excercise to get used to this system I added them. You can find them under the articles section. Up to now I'm quite impressed with drupal.<br />MP3_Compare_Help

<h1><div align="center">Help for MP3-Compare</div></h1>
<h3>Possible options on the 'Your MP3s' and 'Your friends MP3s' tabs:</h3>
[image:514]<br />
<br />
You may enter a path, or select one with the browse button. The program searches for a file
  called 'mp3list.mcz' in the specified directory. On success this file is loaded, otherwise
  the specified directory is scanned. If 'Scan subdirs' is checked, it will scan recursively.
  If 'Add to list' is selected, the files found (file or scan) are added to the current list, so
  you're able to read a whole disc-set in one file.<br />
The button 'FN2TAG' converts the filename(s) of the selected mp3(s) to tags, if they're after
  the scheme 'artist - title'!

<h1><div align="center">Help for MP3-Compare</div></h1>
<h3>Possible options on the 'Your MP3s' and 'Your friends MP3s' tabs:</h3>
[image:514]<br />
<br />
You may enter a path, or select one with the browse button. The program searches for a file
  called 'mp3list.mcz' in the specified directory. On success this file is loaded, otherwise
  the specified directory is scanned. If 'Scan subdirs' is checked, it will scan recursively.
  If 'Add to list' is selected, the files found (file or scan) are added to the current list, so
  you're able to read a whole disc-set in one file.<br />
The button 'FN2TAG' converts the filename(s) of the selected mp3(s) to tags, if they're after
  the scheme 'artist - title'!<br />
The button 'TAG2FN' does exactly the reverse thing, renaming the file to 'Artist - Title'.<br />
Pressing 'Scan' will rescan the currently selected directory.<br />
With 'Search' you can easily search for an mp3 in your mp3list. simply enter the search terms.
mp3compare will do an 'AND' search.<br />

With 'Load list' you can load a list of mp3s which will replace the current list, if 'Add to list'
isn't checked.<br />
With 'Save list as' you can save your list to another than the default name. You can also
select 'HTML' as output format, and a html list of your mp3s will be created.<br />
'Mail list' simply mails the list to a friend. Be sure to check the eMail - Setting on the config tab!<br />
'Cancel' will cancel every running operation - Scanning / Comparing<br />
'Play' plays the currently selected mp3 using Winamp,
'Enqueue' will enqueue it, and 'E and P' will add it to the current playlist and plays it afterwards.<br />
'Exit' will exit the program - but who wants to?? ;-)
<h3>Possibilities in the context menu:</h3>
<table>
<tbody><tr>
<td>[image:517]</td>
<td valign="top">

'Refresh Item': Refreshes currently selected items<br />
'Remove Item after file operation': Will remove the selected items after successful move/copy/del<br />
'Delete, Move, Copy': Does exactly the same as in the windows explorer<br />
'Fileinfo/Edit Tag': Let you edit the ID3 tag for one or more (!!) files, see special section at the bottom of the page<br />
'Normalize Tag': oNe tOtAly UNConvEntional WRITTEN tag -&gt; One Totaly Unconvential Written Tag for Artist and Title
'Play','Enqueue','Enqueue and Play': The same as the tool buttons<br />
</td>
</tr>
</tbody></table>
<h3>Possible options on the result tab:</h3>
[image:515]<br />
<br />

Just self explaining i think. Go will check for duplicates in either your or your friends MP3s. Load/Save
loads a list of results, for example to send your friend a list, he could give you as a gift ;-)<br />
<h3>Possibilities in the context menu:</h3>
<table>
<tbody><tr>
<td>[image:516]</td>
<td valign="top">
'Remove pair from list': Simply removes a pair from the list, no physical harm is done!<br />
'Remove pair after file operation': Will remove the selected pairs after successful move/copy/del<br />
'Delete, Move, Copy': Does exactly the same as in the windows explorer for either the TOP files or 
the BOTTOM files<br />
'Select all': Selects all files<br />
'Play': Plays either TOP or BOTTOM file<br />

</td>
</tr>
</tbody></table>
<h3>Possible options on the config tab:</h3>
[image:520]<br />
<br />
<b>General</b><br />
'Auto save mp3list after scan' will automatically save the list in the default file 'mp3list.mcz'<br />
'Hitbarrier': Selects above which percentage two files are suspected to be the same (for compare/duplicates)<br />
'Show complete path in results': Toggles path in results<br />
'Path to winamp': Your winamp executable. Auto-Determined on first start-up<br />

<b>HTML-List Creation</b><br />
'Relative path to CSS': Points to a Cascading Style Sheet for formatting the list.<br />
'Insert links to files': MP3s will be linked so click in webbrowser opens it<br />
'Relative path': ...<br />
<b>E-Mail Setting</b><br />
For sending your list to a friend, common settings, self-explaining i think<br />
<b>Warn user before</b><br />
Self-explaining, isn't it?<br />
<h3>What you can do in the edit-tag box:</h3>

<table width="100%">
<tbody><tr>
<td width="50%" align="center">[image:518]</td>
<td width="50%" align="center">[image:519]</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<div align="center">Edit a single file</div>
Simply edit the attributes of the file, ok writes them to disk.
</td>
<td>
<div align="center">Edit multiple files at a time</div>
Edits the attributes of multiple files simultaneously. When the checkbox to the right is checked,
the attributes will be written. So you can give all your files the same comment or equalize the
artist names.
</td>
</tr>

</tbody></table>



]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
